<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on c6p - log</title><link>/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on c6p - log</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/docs/learning/exercism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/learning/exercism/</guid><description>Exercism # My exercism profile: c6p
acronym # python Convert a phrase to its acronym. - view
import re def abbreviate(words): &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;Abbreviates words First alphabetic character succeeding nonalphabetic characters is captured, then uppercased. &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; return re.sub(r&amp;#39;[^A-Za-z]*([A-Za-z])[A-Za-z\&amp;#39;]*&amp;#39;, r&amp;#39;\1&amp;#39;, words).upper() all-your-base # javascript Convert a number, represented as a sequence of digits in one base, to any other base. - view
export function convert(arr, from, to) { if (!</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/learning/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/learning/resources/</guid><description>Resources # Select Topic... drawing git windows Select Type... cmdfu tool tutorial Topic Type Resource Detail git tutorial Learn Git Branching Interactive git tutorial, game. git cmdfu Oh Shit, Git!?! For fixing mistakes. windows tool Privatezilla Single click desktop app to perform quick privacy/security check and debloat. windows cmdfu Privacy.sexy Website to copy and paste privacy/security/bloat PowerShell scripts drawing tutorial Bezier game Interactive way to learn drawing perfect bezier curves.</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/ossu/operating_systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/ossu/operating_systems/</guid><description>History # Just Libraries # OS would provide API. Jobs set up and then run in a batch by the operator. Computers were not interactive.
Protection # The idea of system call invented by Atlas computing system. Instead of providing OS routines as a library (procedure call), special instructions to transition into a more formal, controlled process.
window.onload=()=mermaid.initialize({ "flowchart": { "useMaxWidth":true }, "theme": "dark" } ) sequenceDiagram participant U as User Mode participant K as Kernel Mode U-K: trap K-U: return-from-trap Multiprogramming # I/O devices were slow, having a program wait CPU was a waste of time.</description></item></channel></rss>